ACTWU's Research Department Company Records 5619/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- East Will Sportswear Co., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 44)
- East Wind Industries, Inc., 1976 (Box 37, Folder 45)
- Eastco Car Wash/Buffalo (Snyder), NY/(Formerly Arco Car Wash), 1974 (Box 37, Folder 46)
- Eastern Knitting Mills, Inc., 1974 (Box 37, Folder 47)
- Easthampton Clothes (Division of Cable Ind.), 1973 (Box 37, Folder 48)
- Eastman Chemical Products, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 49)
- Easton Clothing, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 50)
- Easton Trouser Co., 1964 (Box 37, Folder 51)
- Eastwood Apparel Ltd., 1968 (Box 37, Folder 52)
- Eaton's of California, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 53)
- Eatonton Manufacturing Co.(cross Reference to Spencer Industries), 1968 (Box 37, Folder 54)
- Alton Eber, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 55)
- Charles Edelman & Son, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 56)
- Eden Industries, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 57)
- Eden Textiles, Division of American Petrochemical Corporation/Memphis, TN, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 58)
- Edgefield Shirt Co., Inc., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 59)
- Edgewood, Inc., 1968 (Box 37, Folder 60)
- Edgewood Knitwear Co., Inc., 1968 (Box 37, Folder 61)
- Edgeworth Mills, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 62)
- James Edmond, Inc., 1974 (Box 37, Folder 63)
- Edmont, Inc., 1970 (Box 37, Folder 64)
- Edmont-Wilson, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 65)
- Edmonton Manufacturing Co., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 66)
- Edna Sportswear, Inc., 1970 (Box 37, Folder 67)
- Edric Manufacturing Co./Columbia, Tennessee, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 68)
- Edwards Manufacturing Co. Inc./Evansville, Ind., 1973 (Box 37, Folder 69)
- Edwards Garment Co., 1974 (Box 37, Folder 70)
- Ralph Edwards Sportswear, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 71)
- Efka Plastics Corp., Bayonne, NJ/also Polytex Corp., Polyprint Corp., 1975 (Box 37, Folder 72)
- Einiger Mills, Inc./NYC., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 73)
- Eisenberg & Eisenberg, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 74)
- Eisenberg Fashions, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 75)
- Eisenberg & O'Hara (see also Marion Maid, Inc.), 1960 (Box 37, Folder 76)
- Eisenberg International, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 77)
- Eisenstein Associates Inc., 1952 (Box 37, Folder 78)
- The Ekmar Corp., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 79)
- El Paso, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 80)
- El Paso Co., 1975 (Box 37, Folder 81)
- Elastic Fabric of America/Ft. Washington, Pa., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 82)
- Elastic Fabrics Co./West Warwick, R. I., 1973 (Box 37, Folder 83)
- Elbe Shirt Co., 1967 (Box 37, Folder 84)
- Electro-Knit Fabrics Inc./Coney Island, NY/Brooklyn, NY, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 85)
- Electro-Knit Fabrics, Ltd. (Canada), 1974 (Box 37, Folder 86)
- Elegant Garments, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 87)
- Elegant Heir, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 88)
- Elegante Fashion Of Miami Inc., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 89)
- Eleganza, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 90)
- Elias, Irving & Co. Inc., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 91)
- Irving Elias & Co.: Hi-Knits Inc., Subsidiary, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 92)
- Elite Dye Works/Drummondville, Quebec, Canada, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 93)
- Elite Laundry, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 94)
- Elizabeth Shirt Company, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 95)
- Elk City Manufacturing Co., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 96)
- Elk Valley Industries, Inc., 1967 (Box 37, Folder 97)
- Elkton Fashion Industries, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 98)
- Ellerbe Manufacturing Co./Ellerbe, NC, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 99)
- Ellery Products Manufacturing Company, Inc../New York, New York, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 100)
- George Elliott, Ltd., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 101)
- Elliott Industries, Inc., 1972 (Box 37, Folder 102)
- Elm Department Store, Inc., 1967 (Box 37, Folder 103)
- Elman, S. Co. (U.S.), 1957 (Box 37, Folder 104)
- Elmer Little & Sons, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 105)
- Elmod Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1966 (Box 37, Folder 106)
- Elmwood Fabrics Co., Inc., 1973 (Box 37, Folder 107)
- Elmvale Worsted Co. & Elmvale Dye Works, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 108)
- Eloesser-Heynemann Co., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 109)
- El-Tech Manufacturing Co., 1966 (Box 37, Folder 110)
- Emco Textile Corp./Paterson, NJ, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 111)
- Emerson Clothing Corp., 1966 (Box 37, Folder 112)
- Emery, Bird, Thayer, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 113)
- Emile Mills, Inc./Midland, N. C., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 114)
- Empire Bias Binding Co., Inc., 1974 (Box 37, Folder 115)
- Emporium Capwell Co., 1975 (Box 37, Folder 116)
- Emporium Corporation (see Breezy Wynn), 1958 (Box 37, Folder 117)
- The Emporium Department Stores, Inc., 1968 (Box 37, Folder 118)
- Endel Pants Company Inc., 1974 (Box 37, Folder 119)
- Energy Manufacturing Co., 1974 (Box 37, Folder 120)
- Enro-at-Ease, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 121)
- Enterprise Dye Works/Woonsocket, R. I., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 122)
- Enterprise Machine & Development Corp., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 123)
- Enterprise Manufacturing Co., 1968 (Box 37, Folder 124)
- Environmentals, Inc., 1972 (Box 37, Folder 125)
- Epplee Ltd. (Division of Well-Made Pants Co.), 1968 (Box 37, Folder 126)
- Equity National Industries Inc./Jordan Carpet Yarns, Inc./Columbus, GA, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 127)
- Equity National Industries, Inc. (Kingston Spinners), 1971 (Box 37, Folder 128)
- Erbe Inc., 1964 (Box 37, Folder 129)
- Erie Clothing Co., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 130)
- Erlanger Cotton Mills (also see Fieldcrest) Lexington, NC, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 131)
- Ernst Neckwear Co./San Francisco, Calif., 1967 (Box 37, Folder 132)
- Erwin Bag Co./Houston, Texas, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 133)
- Erwin Manufacturing Company, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 134)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). (Box 37, Folder 135)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). Arbitrations, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 136)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). Dan Finkle Reports, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 137)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). Financial I (1939-1952) (Box 38, Folder 1)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). General Labor Information 1943-1949, Folder No. 1 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). (Housing Project, 1957-58), 1958 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). Durham, NC: Pillow Case & Sheet Sewers Arbitration, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). Specification Issue, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). Statement to War Labor Board Re: Wage Increase, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). TWUA Statement to War Labor Board on Wage Increase, 6/11/42, 1942 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). Wage Exhibits and Job Specification, 1945-46, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). Durham - Weavers' Arbitration - 1947 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- ERWIN MILLS Inc.: (See also: Burlington Industries, Inc.). Durham/Weavers Dispute (1946) (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Escadrille Shirts Ltd., 1971 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Esgro Inc., 1973 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Esmond Mills, Ltd./Granby, Quebec, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Esmond Mills, Severance Pay Arbitration, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Esquire Knits, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Esquire Pants, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Essex International, Inc., 1971 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Essex Wire Corp./Mt. Airy, NC, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Esskay Manufacturing Co./San Antonio, Texas, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Establissmenten Van Moer (Owned by Work Wear Corp.), 1968 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Esten Dyeing & Finishing Co., Inc./Pawtucket, R.I., 1975 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Etcoknit Goods Processing Co., Inc., 1973 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Etowah Garment Co., 1957 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Etowah Industries, Inc., 1967 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Eudora Garment Manufacturing Corp./Eudora, AR, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Eureka Pants Manufacturing Co., 1966 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Europa Group, Inc. (Boston), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Europe Sport (New York), 1969 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Evan Picone, Inc., 1973 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Evangeline Shoe Co., Ltd./Penetang, Ontario, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- Evangeline Shoe Corp., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Evans & Black Carpet Co.(E & B)/Dallas, Tex. & Dalton, GA, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Evans-Aristocrat Industries, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Evans Manufacturing Co. (see Grifton Manufacturing Co.), 1969 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Evans Rule Co.(Subsidiary Evans Aristocrat Industries)/N. Charleston, SC, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 35)
- Eveready Thread & Yarn Co./Philadelphia, Pa., 1972 (Box 38, Folder 36)
- Evergreen Textiles Inc., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 37)
- Excel Co., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 38)
- Excel IV, Inc./Hawthorne, NJ, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 39)
- Excel Leather Coat Corp., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 40)
- Excello Cravats Inc., 1971 (Box 38, Folder 41)
- Excello Pedigree, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 42)
- Excelsior Underwear Inc./Saluda, SC, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 43)
- Excelsior-Leader, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 44)
- Exchequer by Driway (London, U.K.), 1967 (Box 38, Folder 45)
- Executive Carpets/Dalton, GA, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 46)
- Executive Clothes Inc., 1962 (Box 38, Folder 47)
- Executive Collections, Inc., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 48)
- Executive Jet Aviation Inc., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 49)
- Executive Marketing Corp., 1972 (Box 38, Folder 50)
- Executive Service Co./Pickens, SC, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 51)
- Exeter Industries, Inc./Wilmington, Delaware, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 52)
- Expert Coat Co., 1974 (Box 38, Folder 53)
- Exquisite Fabrics, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 54)
- Exquisite Form Industries, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 55)
- Exquisite Knitwear Ltd., 1970 (Box 38, Folder 56)
- Exx-Calibre Gentlemen's Apparel Inc., 1973 (Box 38, Folder 57)
- F-One Ltd., 1974 (Box 38, Folder 58)
- F&E Garment Co., Ridge Spring, SC, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 59)
- F&M Trim Shop Inc., Newburgh, NY, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 60)
- F&S Fashions (NYC), 1967 (Box 38, Folder 61)
- FDI, Inc. (Formerly Rayco, Inc.)/Pawtucket, R.I., 1975 (Box 38, Folder 62)
- FMC CORPORATION. List of Arbitration Cases, 1943-1976 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- FMC CORPORATION. Summary of Arbitrations at Fiber & Film Divs., 1943-1976 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- FMC CORPORATION. LABOR III - American Viscose Division - 1966-, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- FMC CORPORATION. LABOR: Laboratory Employees, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- FMC CORPORATION. American Viscose Division, Nitro, W. Va., 1970-, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- FMC CORPORATION. Parkersburg, W. Va. Plant Closing, 1974-75, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- FMC CORPORATION. American Viscose Division, Parkersburg, W. Va., 1970-, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- FMC CORPORATION. American Viscose Division, Sylvania Division, Fredricksburg, VA, 1958-69, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- FMC CORPORATION. (Fibers Division) 1974 Negotiations (Box 39, Folder 9)
- FMC CORPORATION. LABOR - 1973 Negotiations (Box 39, Folder 10)
- FMC CORPORATION. AVD 1971 Negotiations (Box 39, Folder 11)
- FMC CORPORATION. Dallas, Texas, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- FMC CORPORATION. American Viscose Division, Fredricksburg, Va. 1968-, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- FMC CORPORATION. American Viscose Division, Front Royal, Va., 1971-75, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- FMC CORPORATION. American Viscose Division, Kennett Fabricators, Kennett Square, PA, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- FMC CORPORATION. American Viscose Division: Financial, 1970-, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- FMC CORPORATION. Fiber Division - General Labor, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- FMC CORPORATION. American Viscose Division #IV: Lewistown, Pa. 1968-, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- FMC CORPORATION. American Viscose Division, Marcus Hook, Pa., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- FMC CORPORATION. American Viscose Division, Meadville, Pa., 1958-, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Fabiano, Ltd., 1966 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Fabens Development Co., Fabens, TX, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Fab-Knit Athletic Manufacturing Co./Waco, Texas (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Fabri-Quilt, Kansas City, MO (Subsidiary of B.C. Christopher & Co.), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Fabric Leather Corporation, Glen Cove, NY, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Fabric Repair & Examining Corp., Passaic, NJ, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Fabrica de Gravatas Doge Limitada, Lisbon, Portugal, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Fabricland, Inc., NYC, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Fabrovin Corporation (formerly Handprints by Zakim, Inc.) Passaic, NJ, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Fabulous Fashions (Olive Hill, Kentucky), 1969 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Faceline Corp., 1970 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Factory Outlet Clothiers Inc., 1964 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Fahey-Brockman, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Fairburn Manufacturing/Fairburn, GA, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Fairchild Tailored Slacks, Inc./Tifton, GA, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Fairchild Trousers, Inc./Tifton, GA, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Fairfield Glove Co., 1963 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- Fairfield Noble Corp., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- Fair Lee Manufacturing Co., 1967 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Fairlawn Textile Processors, Inc., Fair Lawn, NJ, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- Fairmont Knitting Mills/Fairmont, NC, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- Fairpark Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- Fair-Tex Mills, Inc.: Strongwear Pants Co. Division, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- Fairview Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1968 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- Fairweather Co. (CANADA), Toronto, Ont., 1967 (Box 39, Folder 45)
- Falcon Industries, Inc.(NYC), 1964 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- Falcon International Corp. (NYC) (D&B on Falcon Industries), 1967 (Box 39, Folder 47)
- Falk, Robt. J. (NYC), 1966 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- Fall River Clothing Manufacturing Co., 1968 (Box 39, Folder 49)
- Fall River Knitting Mills, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 50)
- FALL RIVER/NEW BEDFORD TEXTILE Manufacturers ASSN. 1944 Arbitration on Superdraft & Interdraft Frames (Box 39, Folder 51)
- FALL RIVER/NEW BEDFORD TEXTILE Manufacturers ASSN. Wage Arbitration-1948 (Ledger file) (Box 39, Folder 52)
- FALL RIVER/NEW BEDFORD TEXTILE Manufacturers ASSN. Wage Arbitration-1952 (Ledger file) (Box 40, Folder 1)
- FALL RIVER/NEW BEDFORD TEXTILE Manufacturers ASSN. Arbitration Award 7/15/52, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Fame Shirtmakers, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- The Family Bargain Centers, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Family Dollar Stores, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Family Fashions, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Famous-Barr, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Famous Cottons Inc., 1960 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Famous-Sternberg, Inc., 1968 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Fancy Pants, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Fanfare Knits, Inc., 1974 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Fanslau Warping & Sizing Corp., 1974 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Far Eastern Textile Ltd., 1970 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- FARAH Manufacturing Co. Inc. Civil Actions, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- FARAH Manufacturing Co. Inc. D&B & Firm Information, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- FARAH Manufacturing Co. Inc. News Clips 1973-76, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- FARAH Manufacturing Co. Inc. NLRB Clips & Strike Info, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- FARAH Manufacturing Co. Inc. News Clips 1964-72, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- FARAH Manufacturing Co. Inc. Annual Reports & 10-K's, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Farmington Manufacturing Co., 1969 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Farragut Fashions, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Fashion Craft Manufacturers Ltd. (Canada), 1962 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Fashion Factory (NYC) (Inactive), 1984 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Fashion Fair Inc. (Cross Reference to Twin Fair Inc.), 1968 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Fashion Footwear/E. Rutherford, NJ (See also Frier Industries), 1973 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Fashion Neckwear, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Fashion Park, Inc. Annual Reports, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- Fashion Park, Inc. D&B, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Fashion Park, Inc. (Rochester, NY) - Firm Info., 1970 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Fashion Park, Inc. - News Clippings, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Fashion Park, Inc. - Severance Pay 1970, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Fashion Prints (New York, NY), 1969 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Fashion Prints (Subsidiary of US Industries Inc., Allentown, PA), 1971 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Fashion Seal Uniform (Huntington, NY), 1974 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- Fashion Sportswear (Los Angeles, CA), 1967 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Fashionbilt Clothes (Philadelphia), 1969 (Box 40, Folder 36)
- Fashionnaire (Chicago IL), 1975 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- Fashions by Wisz (Tupelo, MS), 1976 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- Fatuch Sportswear (El Paso TX), 1975 (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Favilla Knitting Mills, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 40)
- Fawn Togs Inc. (Subsid. of BVD Company), 1967 (Box 40, Folder 41)
- Fayette Manufacturing Company, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 42)
- Fayetteville Shirt Co., Inc., 1965 (Box 40, Folder 43)
- Feather Fabrics, Inc., 1974 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Fechheimer Bros. Co., 1969 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Jerry Feder for Men, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Federal Bag/St. Louis, Mo., 1972 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- FEDERAL'S. Annual Reports, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- FEDERAL'S. News Clippings, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- FEDERATED DEPARTMENT STORES. Annual Reports & Firm Info., 1975 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- FEDERATED DEPARTMENT STORES. Abraham & Strauss, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- FEDERATED DEPARTMENT STORES. Bloomingdale's, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- FEDERATED DEPARTMENT STORES. Bullock's Inc., 1977 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- FEDERATED DEPARTMENT STORES. Fedway, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- FEDERATED DEPARTMENT STORES. Filene's, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- FEDERATED DEPARTMENT STORES. Levy's of Tucson, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- FEDERATED DEPARTMENT STORES. Rike's Division, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- FEDERATED DEPARTMENT STORES. Sanger-Harris, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- FEDERATED DEPARTMENT STORES. Shillito's, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Feinrider, Dennis (La Follette, TN), 1971 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Feinstein, P. & Sons (NYC), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Felco Athletic Wear Co., 1973 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Felco Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1968 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Felco Sports Products, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Feldmuehle A.G., 1975 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Feldt, Max, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Glencoe Fell Co., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Felters Co. #2 Fin. & Gen. 1970-, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Fentress Industries Inc., 1975 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Leon Ferenbach Silk Mill, Johnson City, TN, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- David Ferguson, Ltd., 1963 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Franklin Ferguson Co., 1972 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- R. H. Ferguson Manufacturing Co., 1969 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Fergusson Atlantic Ltd., 1969 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Carl A. Ferrazz, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- Fiber Containers Inc./Buffalo, NY, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- Fiber Glass Industries, Inc./Amsterdam, NY, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 34)
- Fiberglas Canada Limited/Guelph, Ont., 1975 (Box 41, Folder 35)
- Fiberglas Industries/Amsterdam, NY, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 36)
- Fibers International Corporation/Guyama, P.R., 1975 (Box 41, Folder 37)
- Fiberspun, Inc./Staunton, VA, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 38)
- Field Bros., 1972 (Box 41, Folder 39)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Annual Reports, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 40)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Fin. & Gen., 1973 (Box 41, Folder 41)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. News Clippings, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 42)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Wages - All Plants, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 43)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Towel Mill, Fieldale, VA (1939-1974) (Box 41, Folder 44)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Greenville, NC, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 45)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Morgan Carpet Mills, Laurel Hill, NC, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 46)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Mount Holly, NC, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 47)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. NC Finishing Co., Salisbury NC (Erlanger)(From 1950)(F/L II), 1966 (Box 41, Folder 48)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Smithfield, NC (1973 Election) (Box 41, Folder 49)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Spray, NC Synthetic Fabrics Mill (1956 Rate Increase) (Box 41, Folder 50)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. General Labor IV (1958-1971) (Box 41, Folder 51)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Finishing Plant, Eden, NC (1941-1967) (Box 42, Folder 1)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Bedspread Department IV, Eden, NC ('1958-1973) (Box 42, Folder 2)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Blanket Mill, Eden, NC (1958-1972) (Box 42, Folder 3)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Blanket Finishing Mill, Eden, NC, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Karastan Rug Mill, Eden, NC (1958-1970), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Alexander Manufacturing Co., Forest City, NC (Formerly Erlanger), 1964 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Erlanger Textile Corp., NYC, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Winchester Spinning Corp., Asheville, NC, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. (Nye-Wait Co. Division) Auburn, NY, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Sheeting Mill, Eden, NC (1958-'73), 1973 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Warehouse, Eden, NC (1941-'53), 1953 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Bleachery, Eden, NC (1941-'51), 1951 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- FIELDCREST MILLS. Inc. Muscogee Mills Division, Columbus, GA, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- J. M. Fields (Department Store Division Food Fair), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Joyner Fields, Inc., 1967 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- W. E. Fife Co./Salt Lake City, Utah, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Fillings, Inc., 1973 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Filtertek, Inc./Hebron, Ill., 1973 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Finale, Inc., 1970 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Finchley's Fifth Avenue (Men's & Women's Specialty), 1967 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Findlay Industries, Inc./Findlay, Ohio, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Fine Clothing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Finecraft Knitwear Corp., 1970 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Finesilver Manufacturing Co., 1975 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Fingerhut Corp./Cornwall, Ontario, Canada, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Finishing Enterprises, Inc./Niagara Falls, NY, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- Finkelberg Co., 1971 (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Jacob Finkelstein & Sons, Inc., 1965 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- Finleigh Clothes, Ltd., 1973 (Box 42, Folder 29)
- Fireside Fabrics (Canada), Ltd./St. Jean, Que., Canada, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 30)
- Firestone Plastics Co./General, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 31)
- Firestone Rethread Corp./Columbus, Ohio, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 32)
- Firestone Synthetic Fibers Co./Hopewell, Virginia, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 33)
- Firestone Textiles/New Bedford, MA, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 34)
- Firma Compernole en Zoon (Belgium), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 35)
- First Boston Corp., 1975 (Box 42, Folder 36)
- First Combined Enterprises, Inc., 1975 (Box 42, Folder 37)
- First Hartford Corp. - Wyandotte Arbitration, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 38)
- First Hartford Corp. - (Wyandotte Industries, Subsidiary), 1974 (Box 42, Folder 39)
- First Hartford Corp. - Textile Division (Formerly: Wyandotte Industries), 1974 (Box 42, Folder 40)
- First Hartford Corp. - Textile Division (Formerly: Wyandotte Worsted), 1970 (Box 42, Folder 41)
- First State Bank of San Leandro, Calif., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 42)
- Fischer Kiddie Coat Corp., 1967 (Box 42, Folder 43)
- Fischer Mills (Subsidiary of Cluett, Peabody & Co.), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 44)
- Fisher-Price Toys, Inc./E. Aurora, NY, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 45)
- Fisher Scientific Co., 1975 (Box 42, Folder 46)
- Fit Rite Pants Co., Inc., 1972 (Box 42, Folder 47)
- Fitzgerald Mills/Fitzgerald, GA, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 48)
- Fitzpatrick's Nun's Apparel, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 49)
- The 5770 Corporation, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 50)
- Five Star Uniform, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 51)
- Flagg-Utica Corp., 1962 (Box 42, Folder 52)
- Flair Formal Shirts, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 53)
- Flair Sportswear Industries, Inc., 1970 (Box 42, Folder 54)
- Flair Cleaners, Inc., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 55)
- Fleetline Industries, Inc./Garland, N. Carolina, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 56)
- Fleisher Fabrics, Inc./Waterbury, Conn., 1974 (Box 42, Folder 57)
- Fleming & Jaffe, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 58)
- Paterson Fletcher, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 59)
- Flex Knit, Inc./Syracuse, NY, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 60)
- Flexees (Division of BVD), 1967 (Box 42, Folder 61)
- Flexi - Pak, Inc., 1968 (Box 42, Folder 62)